ETHAN **SUM**

https://xthxnsxm.github.io/



OBJECTIVE

Current full-time university student studying computer science with a reputable diligence matched by none. Excellent communication skills, a positive mentality, along with previous experience in event organization will make a perfect fit for any role. Always up to the challenge.



EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree | University of Toronto

2021 – PRESENT Current GPA: 4.0

High School Diploma | St. Marcellinus Secondary School

2017 - 2021

Grade 12 Average: 95.0%

Maintained honor roll status for all 4 years of high school while participating in several after-school activities such as band, drumline, and the badminton club.



EXPERIENCE

Event Organizer | St. Marcellinus Secondary School 3/2019 – 5/2019

- Participated in strategy development and planning to grow program and activities
- Fostered collaborative efforts to schedule, host, and facilitate events
- Collaborated with others to create food and entertainment for guests

Peer Tutor | St. Marcellinus Secondary School

9/2020 - 6/2021

- Gave back to the community by guiding younger students in their academic studies
- Explained difficult concepts in a more digestible manner
- Inspired younger students and gave them the confidence to succeed

X

SKILLS

- Java
- Python
- HTML

- CSS
- Javascript
- Github



ACTIVITIES

In my free time I love to develop code and explore music. My most recent project is my own personal website https://xthxnsxm.github.io/! If you want a taste of my music, here is my YouTube channel https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCtaVOcpXiVXI4fOTq4OW9xg.